The Sweetest Christmas is a romance, tv movie film directed by Terry Ingram.
After breaking up with her long-term boyfriend just before the holidays,
passionate baker Kylie reconnects with her high school sweetheart, Nick.
Thanks to their newly rekindled friendship, Kylie uses Nick’s restaurant to prepare for a gingerbread
baking competition with a large cash prize that would help her open her own bakery.
Kylie, played by Lacey Chabert.
Nick, played by Lea Coco.
Ralphie, played by Jonathan Adams.
Bobby, played by Brenden Sunderland.
Tina, played by Lara Gilchrist.
Alex, played by Lane Edwards.
Christopher McNally (born November 8, 1988) is a Canadian-born actor most noted for his role as
Lucas Bouchard in the Hallmark Channel series When Calls the Heart (2019–present).
The tone is emotional.